( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
I'm reporting from Junlin Group.
According to insiders,
Shen Tingyuan, Chairman of Junlin Group,
recently suffered a sudden stroke
due to emotional agitation
while handling
internal company decisions.
He was rushed to
the hospital for emergency treatment,
and his condition
is still under observation.
Prior to this,
the largest shareholder, Shen Gu,
will call a general meeting
to elect a new
chairman for Junlin Group.
Are you feeling hot?
You're sweating quite a bit.
Are you in pain?
Shen Hao,
I understand how you feel right now.
Your dad will get better.
What's the point of getting better?
Waking up just to face his own failure?
He'd be better off dead.
Hao.
Stop lying to me.
What a pitiful face,
so good at pretending.
You fooled me for eight whole years.
Eight years!
So, Wanxin, please
stop acting,
okay?
Hao,
calm down.
Before anything irreversible happens,
there's still room to fix this.
What do you mean by nothing happened?
If it weren't for Shen Gu,
I would be the one marrying you.
Me!
It's all because of Shen Gu.
All my misfortunes are because of him.
I'm telling you,
as long as Shen Gu dies...
Shen Hao!
This has nothing to do with Shen Gu.
Even without him,
I would never have married you.
Even if I have to
declare Minghui bankrupt,
I will cut ties with you.
I'm right here.
If you have the guts, come at me.
You're still defending him?
I'm the one who was hurt.
Me!
Listen here, once Shen Gu disappears,
Junlin will be mine.
Minghui will be mine.
And you are mine. Mine!
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 26=
(Let Tragedies Never Happen Again)
There's still no news
of Miss Lin from Gang City.
Miss Lin
sacrificed herself.
Sacrificed?
President of the Shen City
Chamber of Commerce,
Shen Gu, has passed away.
Shen Gu is dead.
Grandfather.
Hello, Xi.
Mr. Changhe.
Grandfather.
Grandfather, please don't worry.
Wanxin will be fine.
But before Wanxin returns,
you must take care of your health.
The police are investigating.
Shen Gu has landed in Gang City,
and he's currently
on his way back to us.
Yes, and tell
Shen Gu to be careful.
Wanxin and Shen Gu just got together.
Nothing else must happen to them.
Don't worry, Grandfather.
Everything will be okay.
Hello,
it's Shen Gu.
Shen Gu, I'll give you half an hour.
If you don't want Xu Wanxin to die,
get over here right now.
Shen Gu, don't come!
He's lost his mind! Call the police!
Fine. I agree.
But you must ensure Wanxin's safety.
Then, you'd better hurry.
After all, I've already gone mad,
and I don't have much patience.
Gently!
This is my wife.
Hello?
Fang Hongsheng,
there's news.
Shen Hao kidnapped Wanxin.
He's out of control now.
He demanded to see me alone.
I'm notifying the police right now.
I'll have someone track
your car's location in real-time.
Okay.
Be careful.
Shen Hao, let her go!
Take one more step,
and I'll kill her.
Fine.
I won't move.
Don't touch her.
Beat him!
Shen Gu!
Wanxin!
Shen Gu forced my hand.
Wanxin.
Are you okay, Wanxin?
(Gang City Central Hospital)
Shen Gu...
Shen Gu.
You're awake.
Wanxin...
You're finally awake.
You scared me to death.
You know,
if the jade pendant
hadn't blocked the knife for you,
I would have...
It's okay.
It's all over now.
Don't move.
You have a stab wound on your chest.
Lie down.
Just stay still.
Wanxin,
it's all right.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
I was just dreaming.
I dreamed you were calling my name.
And then, I woke up.
Don't cry.
How is he? Is he out of danger?
Fine.
How is it? Is he out?
It's okay now.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪